import ICard from '../Models/ICard'

const BasicList = [
  {
    id: 0,
    front: "Basic List",
    back: "Click the number that best indicates how well you know the word, with 4 being the highest"
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    front: 'بالتاكيد',
    back: 'For sure/Definetly',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    front: 'مصدر / مصادر (p)',
    back: 'Source',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    front: 'لاحظت',
    back: 'Noticed',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    front: 'زلزالٌ قوي يضرب #هايتي، ويسفر عن سقوطِ مئات الضحايا في جنوب غرب الجزيرة، بحسب وكالة "فرانس 24" والرئيس الأميركي جو #بايدن يعرض المساعدة.',
    back: 'A strong earthquake strikes Haiti, resulting in hundreds of casualties in the south west of the island, according to France 24, and US President Joe Biden offers help.'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    front: 'تحديد',
    back: 'Select/Choose/Set',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    front: 'انتهيت',
    back: 'I finished',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    front: 'موضوع',
    back: 'Theme/Subject/Topic',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    front: 'عام',
    back: 'General/Public',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    front: 'تحدثت',
    back: 'I spoke',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    front: 'مشرف',
    back: 'Supervisor',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    front: 'قد',
    back: 'May/May be',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    front: 'قائمة',
    back: 'List',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    front: 'المراجع',
    back: 'References',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    front: 'يوجد',
    back: 'There are / exists',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    front: 'أتمنى',
    back: 'I wish',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    front: "قدام مرايتها عادي بتدلع براحتها",
    back: "In front of her mirror, she is normal, she is comforted by her comfort"
  }
];

export default BasicList;